Well, I don't know ‭what to tell you, Grandpappy.
我不知道该说什么  姥爷
I guess your daughter found a real man.
看来你女儿找了个真汉子
Of all people.
偏偏是你
Why couldn't it be Flint?
为什么不是弗林特
I liked Flint.
我喜欢弗林特
Well, that's a lovely sentiment.  That's almost as loving as when you had a robot...
这真是感人  跟你让机器人拿枪指着我的头
point a gun to my head.
一样有爱
I didn't want to hurt anybody.
我没想伤害任何人
It's fine. It's the first move you made
没事的  那是你第一次
that actually made me respect you a little bit.
让我对你稍微起了点敬意
It's my kind of move.
我也会做出这种事
And this place, 80 years from now,  I'd survived on moves like that.
八十年后在这里  我能凭类似的举动活下来
'Cause it was kill or be killed.
不是杀人就是被杀
I know Johnson's still mad at me about the whole "selling her into slavery" thing,
我知道约翰逊还在气我  "把她当成奴隶卖掉"的事
but you got to play the long game, or else the whole world is gonna be a vacancy, right?
但你得把眼光放长远  不然整个世界都会变成空位  对不对